Valentine!!!
They surprised me across the street!
Wow!
I'm gonna have to ask you to stop.
Are you sure you're okay with this?
What are you ricochetting?
Wow! That's so good!
It's done!
It's beautifully done!
Smells so good!
Oh no!
It's baked!
It's Tochiaibana baked in Tochigi prefecture!
I became a Tochigi future ambassador the other day.
I'll advertise it here already.
Tochiaika, this is a new arrival.
It's a new arrival, but it's so sweet and delicious.
If you come to Tochigi, you can buy it.
I'm sure you can find them anywhere in Tochigi, so please try them for sure!
Strawberries from Tochigi Prefecture!
Look at them! They are so cute! They're like strawberries!
Oh, look out!
The hole is hidden.
I look like a strawberry.
Yummy, yummy, yummy! Look at that! Yummy!
Oh, yummy!
This is better.
This is what they're selling, isn't it? I put so much on it! Looks good! This one looks better!
It looks better with a lot of food on it.
I like that you can imagine the line of movement.
You know what I mean? Can you feel it?
Let's make it a heart!
Please!
You'll hear it when I get out.
Yum!
It's not easy to make candy like this... and it takes a lot of time and effort. You have to really like it.
I also like to get better.
Just in time.
Very close.
So it's done!
I finished it!
It's done!
It was quite hard work, because there were some holes, but look at this...
You can't tell, can you?
I hid it, but I'm sure it tastes good, so as long as it tastes good, it's ok.
I'm sure you will praise the taste of this dish.
It looks so good!
It looks great!
It's amazing!
I think it's genius!
I think he's a genius.
I get carried away easily.
I get carried away.
I'll take it back.
I'm a genius and it's delicious.
It's delicious.
Like this.
I'm sorry I messed up.
I'm sorry I messed up... but this is even better!
I'm sure you'll fall in love with it if you get it.
I'm sure I'll fall in love with it if I get it.
I thought it might have been too much, so I added a bit of refreshing orange.
It's great!
I hope you like it!
Can I just do this once?
How do you do this?
How do you do it? How do you do it?
Do what?
My eyes?
Yes!
It's a bit of a stretch.
Okay.
Again!
I'm sorry!
See you!
No problem.
Great. I'm so happy to get this.
You're so lucky.
They're so lucky.
Only a mixed group of men and women can do that.
They really are.
It's nice.
I give up.
Okay.
And the rest
Oh, An-kun's makeup!
Wow, it's really Anri!
Oh my god, it's really Anri, really Anri, I recognized her right away!
I'm so amazed at the results!
I understand a lot.
Are you sure about that? You're not a player, how worried are you? It's done!
I haven't decided who plays which note yet, but I've made four.
Four are done!
Three are done!
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go!
Wow, look at that, all at once, I feel like a gateau chocolat!
Wow, that's amazing!
It's really blowing in the wind!
I wonder why... maybe it's the air conditioning.
You guys have been lying to me.
I've been lying so much! What am I going to do? Only one of us is nervous!
Okay, that's enough.
It's done!
It smells so good!
But there's a little bit of this smell.
It's been in my house for about 4 days now.
I'm sure it will smell again afterwards.
But it's so delicious!
I can't wait for you to try it!
Yay!
Fast forward!
I don't know what to do.
One more!
If there's a smiley face, it's black.
A black smiley face. Wait a minute.
Surely this will do.
Ah, I'm done...
You're adding more, and I'm saying, "Oh, shit," and then I'm adding more.
I kind of like it.
He's cute.
That's Haruma.
And I've recreated his soft and springy body.
I finished it.
It's finished!
I was going to draw a bear
I was going to draw a bear, but
I was going to draw four people, but I just wanted to play with them a little bit
I was going to draw bears, but I wanted to play with them a little bit, so I ended up drawing four of them.
Wow, but they really are a little too childish.
I'm still a little embarrassed about it.
But I'm glad I finished it.
Well then, it's finished!
I finished it!
It's so, so, so cute!
I think everyone is pretty satisfied with how it turned out.
It looks good.
And the final result?
It's like this, guys. It turned out great.
I'm going to give it to all the boys right away.
Ready!
So, here we go!
I'm going to give them to the boys now.
Aren't you excited?
I can't stop the excitement!
I can't wait to hand it over, so I'm going to call the boys right away.
Thank you for your hard work! Good work!
Thank you for your hard work!
No, I didn't know there was a place like this.
Nothing's gone wrong.
What?
I'm scared.
Nothing's wrong, but it's okay. It's okay.
Go, go, go.
Okay, bye.
What's in February?
Haruma's birthday.
Oh no, it's there.
In mid-February, right?
Yes, but... but...
Aren't you all nervous?
You're all nervous.
Actually? Actually?
I'm a little nervous. Something happened on February 15th.
I'm gonna be... I can't sleep at night! I can't sleep at night! Valentine's Day is coming.
That's what I mean!
It's Valentine's Day!
Everyone wants a valentine, right?
Yes!
Give me a valentine, give me a valentine!
I want it!
So often the sweet, sweet girls
For all of you
I've made it!
We have made it!
I made it!
You made it by hand?
I did!
So, since we're all so excited and can't stop talking...
I'm going to bring it right away!
Last year, I got a commercial one, which made me happy, but I also got one for TikTok.
But this time, I'm even more happy to hear that they made them for TikTok.
I'm even more excited to hear that they made it properly this time. Seriously.
Yes, I brought it!
We all put a lot of love into making one item for each of you, and I'd like you all to guess who made which one.
Was it the one I just brought?
Seriously, it doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter, it doesn't matter, it doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter.
Heh.
I'm kind of curious about this.
I'm kind of curious about this, okay?
Okay, okay, okay.
I'm curious.
It's got strawberries on it.
I think it's Eechi, who loves strawberries.
That's what I thought.
That's a strawberry.
Maybe it's a fake.
I thought it might be Eechi, too.
I see.
This one.
This donut.
You don't know who this is, do you? Huh? Huh? This one, this doughnut.
I don't know who this is.
I just thought, "Who is this?
Yuna made these.
And this, this is Miyu
Miyu made this one.
Haruma, Haruma, Haruma, Haruma, this might be bitterness
Maybe that's why it takes a name.
How about this? Maybe it's a taste, maybe that's why it has a name
How about this?
I don't know.
And I'm pretty sure I saw this.
This reminds me of when I was in my pink costume.
First of all, I put on this pink heart thing.
Andie, you're the only one who can do it, right?
I see.
No, I don't know.
The package looks like it's from Icchi.
It looks like they put something in the paper.
I don't know.
I think I like this kind of thing.
Oh!
Gohatsu!
Bon appétit.
Bon appétit!
Let's start with the donuts.
Donuts first?
Let's start with the doughnut.
It's got tangerine peel.
Is it?
How fancy?
I don't put tangerine peel in my...
I don't often put tangerine peel in my food, so I'm afraid of being electrified.
Bon appétit.
Oh...
It smells like citrus.
Yes, yes...
Amazing.
Colorful.
Mmm-hmm.
Is that a little pale on your face?
You're right.
Stop it.
Oh, my God.
I think I might taste something like Eechi.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
That's so weird.
It tastes like citrus, it tastes like citrus, it tastes like citrus, it tastes like citrus, it tastes like citrus, it tastes like citrus, it tastes like citrus.
It tastes so simple.
Is there any candy that I know of?
This is it!
It's delicious!
It's doughy and fluffy.
It's got a little something in it too.
It's like a dough to match the dough.
that goes well with the dough.
on top of it is just right.
If it's the right thing, it means that it's been carefully researched
and made by a good chef.
I think it's very tasty and can be served in a restaurant!
Which one do you want next?
This one.
Let's have this one with strawberries on it.
The one with strawberries on it.
It's definitely the first one.
It's definitely strawberry.
I love strawberries.
Ichi eats strawberries while he's making something.
I don't know.
Maybe this is foreshadowing that he's from Tochigi.
Wow.
No, it's that way.
And look at this reaction...
Who is it?
I mean, even if you bought a regular strawberry...
I probably wouldn't be able to keep one.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Did you get it?
Bon appétit!
Nice mouth.
Everyone has a good mouth.
I'm still eating.
It's good.
Delicious
This one tastes like Eechi's.
It's all Eechi's.
Ici makes the most delicious sweets.
If you think the other girls can't do it, you're wrong.
Yes, you are.
Don't do that.
Is it possible that it's all Ichi-chan's?
Oh, maybe that's it.
It's delicious.
The dough isn't too sweet, so it's good with whipped cream.
Delicious.
I think he really meant something like this.
The dough is not too sweet.
The cream has just the right amount of sweetness.
and the tartness of the strawberries is just right.
It's so delicious!
Oh!
Perfect!
Great, I don't have an edible food report.
Let's try this next time.
This?
He's probably picturing a face.
Wait, don't you want some of this?
I want to take one of these home.
Wait a minute. Here.
That's a cute one.
I'm sure it was a cheek, but now it's come off, don't you want one? I want to take one of these home with me.
I want to take one of these home with me.
I got it off!
I'm sure it was Miyu-chan's!
Am I the only one? Did you write your name on it?
It's got the answer written on it.
Miyu, right?
I'm sure of this one.
This one was surprisingly good.
I want it!
You're right, I love the members, and this is my favorite.
It's so cute!
You haven't eaten it yet.
Wow!
It's like chiffon cake!
I want to take one home!
I have to eat as much of it as possible without ruining my face.
It's in there too.
Really?
It's chiffon cake?
Like Hondan chocolat.
It's not chiffon cake.
I don't even know what it's called anymore.
I've never had all of them.
It's my kind of cake. It's moist.
I like pies and tarts... moist.
Who are you?
Amu recently made this.
Do you see the resemblance? I don't think so.
It's just mine.
It reminds me of the old days.
It's nice.
I was Nico, so I could be anyone.
But you're so cute.
That's funny.
It's good.
Can you finish it?
It's a big one.
You want it all?
It's big.
You know what?
You'll feel like you've earned it.
It's so moist and thick.
Oh, my God.
It's well made, guys.
Well made, guys
Well made, everyone
Well made, guys. Well made, guys.
Are you eating all of them?
I love it.
I'm gonna get one of these.
I'm gonna put it on my phone or something.
I'll put it on my phone or something.
I really like this one, and I can only see it through the stellner.
Which one? What's this?
It's a gateau chocolat.
Yeah, seriously, it's my favorite.
Can any of you make gateau chocolat?
So, someone who knows that I like gateau chocolat made it.
Maybe it's just a coincidence.
Is there one left?
I haven't eaten it yet.
The big one.
You're late.
Because everything else is chocolate.
There's something in this one, too.
Raw chocolate?
I can't tell.
It's frustrating that I can't tell you.
But there's a little too much chocolate on this one.
I did a little.
I feel bad.
It was so chocolatey.
Yuck!
Yuck.
But the three I've had so far...
I mean, there's chocolate, but it's like a sweet.
but this was amazing chocolate!
I know what you mean.
It was delicious.
It tasted like chocolate.
It was rich.
It was the best.
So many hearts.
I'm pretty sure that's Annie Sasaki.
No way.
You can't go this far.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, no? I can't go this far.
I'm sorry.
That was rude.
What's that?
I guess...
I guess the stronger the love for the members, the bigger it gets.
What? There's a love letter in here.
Wow!
That's great, Isshin!
I'm so happy for you.
I thought it was a dream.
It's not in there.
Oh, no, this is for real.
It's not here.
What? Am I the only one who got it? Maybe you're right.
Oh, yeah, you won!
I think Ichi is laughing at this. Oh, really? I'm the only one? Maybe it's... Yes! Bingo! Yiche is laughing so hard.
I'm the only one who won?
Bon appétit!
You eat like that, like rice.
Haruma eats like rice.
They're here.
What's going on?
Does it look like rice?
But it's nice when it's big. If it's small, it's nice to be cared for.
If it's big, I'll be very happy if it's big.
The chocolate inside is amazing.
As expected of Kouei-kun.
I can see how much you've improved, Mr. Koei.
It's going up! Do you think anyone else is going up?
This one has bitter chocolate on the bottom.
It's bitter and a little mature.
It's bitter and a little mature. It's bitter and a little bit mature.
So I think it must be one of the older members.
It's very mature.
Since Anri Suzuki just did, I think, oh, no, I think, since Ms. Iizuka just did, I think Anri Sasagi is the best choice.
I think it's the other way around.
I think she's the best one. I think she's the best one.
I think it's a win-win situation.
No, no, no, I think it's a hit.
On the back side, maybe...
What's wrong with this?
Maybe they're going to put that in there.
Maybe that's what he's trying to do.
No, even if it is, I think it's a hit. Maybe on the back side, maybe it's, "What if I have some left over?
Even if that's the case, I think it's a "Y".
Well then...
Hmm.
That's a lot of eechi.
That's for sure.
All of them in one battle.
All eechi.
I don't know what eechi tastes like.
If you make a mistake, it's not somebody's fault, it's everybody's fault.
And then we'll all fade away.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
They'll be gone.
Then maybe they'll edit it out.
I think the cupcake portrait is of Miu, I think it's her, I think it's her, I think it's her, I think it's her, I think it's her, I think it's her, I think it's her, I think it's her, I think it's her, I think it's her...
I think the cupcake portrait is of Myu-chan.
I think so, too.
I think so too.
Then guess who's the doughnut.
I think the doughnut is Yuna Yajima.
Oh, really?
I think the doughnut is my brother.
I see.
Maybe I don't know.
I think it's either that or a doughnut, bro.
He always puts citrus in his doughnuts.
I think it's Sasaki Yannri. I'm thinking...
I see.
You never know.
Mm-mm-mm-mm-mm-mm...
Wait, aren't we reading too much into it?
I don't think so.
This is Eechi, right?
Definitely!
Oh, no?
I think it's Eechi.
Definitely!
But I think it's Eechi, too.
Me, then. That's EACH one, then.
I think this package is really useful.
I know, I know, I know! I thought it was EACH, but the package looks like it could be useful. - I get it! - I know it! I'm sure! - Definitely!
Wait a minute, isn't the package Yuna Yajima?
Aah! Yes, yes, yes! - I know that one!
Yes, yes! - I was just thinking.
I thought for a minute, "This is definitely going to work! - No, it's like, gâteau au chocolat.
This is definitely going to work! - This one definitely goes!
Don't let that decide you! - I'm sure - I'm sure - I'm sure they're making gâteau au chocolat...
Yes, it's very - it's very Izu Cal.
So, Yuna-chan, this is...
Miyu
Anri
Ichi
Izu Cal's
Yuna-chan
OK
Let's do it!
I want to start with the face cupcakes.
Wait, who is this?
It depends on whether this is Miyu-chan or not
A big upheaval!
I have a feeling it's going to be a big storm!
Seino
Who is the cupcake in the portrait?
Yes!
That's great!
Now we're about to fade out.
Well, well, well.
I made this with love for each and every one of you and with each and every face in mind!
Thank you so much!
I made this with each and every one of your faces in mind... thank you!
I'm so glad
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
I'm in danger, I'm in danger, I'm in danger
I'm afraid I won't get them all.
The way that picture looks...
Right?
Miu Fujisaki's drawings.
The way she jokes around with me...
It's true.
Did I go a little too deep?
Well, you could say that.
It's just a question of whether the donut is Sasaki Anri or not.
I'm wondering if it's Anri Sasaki.
Let's see.
Who made the donuts?
Yes! Nooooo... Not bad! You missed everyone! Please come back!
Once, I made a birthday cake for Issei.
That time, it was really... how do you say?
Was it powerful?
Wasn't it powerful enough for you, Ichi?
It was a whole cake!
I'm so disappointed.
Bummer.
What the hell is this?
So far, I've missed everything.
I don't know what to do.
I don't know.
I mean, I was so sure that this was it.
I thought there might be too much chocolate.
So I thought I'd put something light and refreshing.
So I went with orange.
That's great.
I got what you were trying to do.
I think I got the idea, but I'm thinking about it.
I see what you're getting at.
That's a good position. I didn't think of that.
This one, this one, this one.
Okay, let's do this next one.
I'm wondering who it is.
Then, isn't this Yuna Yajima?
Who made the strawberry sponge cake?
I did!
Eee...
It was me!
Wow!
You have a habit of erasing the next one, don't you?
You were doing it.
You were doing it. - That's right!  - I told you... You're right! You said it!
You said it!
Push it! Push it!
Oh, man, I missed everything.
I missed everything.
I'm a little tiny, you know.
I made them small enough to eat.
I used the strawberries from Tochigiken!
I used Tochigiken's Tochiaica!
Here they are!
You read too much into it.
Did you read too much into this? We did.
This was the cheapest thing I've ever seen.
Baggage buy 1%.
I'm using strawberries.
We should have thought this through a little more.
I should have thought about this a little more
This is, this is...
Um, if it's a reasonable plan, that means it's the right plan.
I see.
So, that would be two correct answers.
That's right.
Let's see...
Who made the gâteau au chocolat?
Yes!
Yay!
Hey!
I knew it was Anri Sasaki!
That's right.
You missed it!
Amazing! That's great!
We were all so mad. - We didn't hit anything! Oh, my gosh! Oh, my God! We're all in over our heads.
We didn't hit anything.
Oh, man!
We only guessed at looking.
You're right!
It's, uh, gâteau au chocolat with truffles inside.
Truffle chocolate, ah!
That was so good!
It was really good!
You know, people are eating it, right?
You know, people are saying it's delicious.
I'm like, "Yay!
I can't be happy about it.
That's true.
I see.
Then, this is...
Akira Sasaki
Speaking of me...
I care about how it looks.
I'm more concerned about the toppings than the food itself, like putting picks on it, even though I don't eat it...
But everything was delicious, everything was delicious.
We really appreciate you taking the time to make it for us, that's what makes us most happy.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
That's great.
Is it possible that March 15th is the day we...
Why 15?
Why 15?  Why are you 15 days late?
I'm looking forward to it. - What? But that means...
Does that mean you're gonna make it?
Because I got it.
No, I'm just saying, you know... you know, the store-bought stuff...
The store-bought one.
I'll give it back. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
As this.
Okay. If you want it so bad, I'll give you my own.
I don't want it.
I really don't want it.
You really don't.
Really don't.
Don't do it.
You really shouldn't do that.
Was it good?
It was delicious.
Thank you.
I can do it.
We worked hard.
So I'm glad you ate it.
Thank you very much.
You know...
I usually cook with my mom by my side.
But this time, my mom wasn't here, so I had to cook by myself.
I practiced twice at home, and today I finally got to cook for the first time.
I was so happy that everyone enjoyed it, so I will make it again!
Yay!
I put a lot of love into making it, and everyone loved how delicious and tasty it was.
I felt so happy that it was worth it!
I was told I wasn't the best cook, but I don't know if everyone enjoyed the food.
I don't know if they liked it or not, but they ate it right in front of me.
But it was fun to watch them eat the food I made in front of my eyes.
I would like to do it again someday.
Yay!
I really couldn't cook or make sweets.
After we decided to do a Valentine's Day project, I practiced three times.
I practiced three times.
At first, I wanted to give people something delicious to eat.
I didn't want to offer something I couldn't eat.
But I was so happy when they said it was delicious.
But it was delicious.
Thank you very much.
That's all for this Valentine's Day project.
Thank you for the food!